<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Better Life</string>

    <string name="share_value">This app is recommended for being very high efficient healthcare in the current period. It is also capable detecting Leukemia Disease and Brain Tumor with quite high probability. Please download and install the app. \nLink: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.betterlife.</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open Navigation Drawer</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close Navigation Drawer</string>

    <!--On Boarding Screen-->
    <string name="first_heading">Detect Leukemia diseases and Brain Tumor</string>
    <string name="second_heading">Get necessary treatment</string>
    <string name="third_heading">Book an appointment with the right doctor</string>
    <string name="fourth_heading">Get medicines delivered to your doorstep</string>
    <string name="fifth_heading">Keep your Medical history handy</string>

    <string name="first_desc">Detect Leukemia diseases and brain tumor is they exist or not sadknddsf af dsfdf dsfdsf</string>
    <string name="second_desc">sfasdf gfsdg dg grtg dh dhgf j ghjhg j jj j gj gj gy ujyg jyj</string>
    <string name="third_desc">dfggffd hdh ty hth t h yth ft h fdfdadafd ada d wd w daw d wad aw d</string>
    <string name="fourth_desc"> cdv f gh uuyi yg  das d a ghgki l ho;  lj d ffdsa f s f DS </string>
    <string name="fifth_desc">sad fg fj  uk l k  hgfs das d sa fsaefrg r th y hyf fc b xf d h df hfgjfgk hjgh jm hmn h nfgb gb db fb f</string>


    <string name="about_brain_tumor1_desc"> A brain tumor is a mass or growth of abnormal cells in your brain. Many different types of brain tumors exist. Some brain tumors are noncancerous (benign), and some brain tumors are cancerous (malignant). Brain tumors can begin in your brain (primarybrain tumors), or cancer can begin in other parts of your body and spread to your brain as secondary (metastatic) brain tumors.
    \n\nHow quickly a brain tumor grows can vary greatly. The growth rate as well as the location of a brain tumor determines how it will affect the function of your nervous system.\n\nBrain tumor treatment options depend on the type of brain tumor you have, as well as its size and location.</string>

    <string name="brainTumorTreatmentText1">Treatment for a brain tumor depends on the type, size and location of the tumor, as well as your overall health and your preferences.</string>

    <string name="brainTumorTreatmentText2">If the brain tumor is located in a place that makes it accessible for an operation, your surgeon will work to remove as much of the brain tumor as can be done safely.
        \nSome brain tumors are small and easy to separate from surrounding brain tissue, which makes complete surgical removal possible. Other brain tumors can\'t be separated from surrounding tissue or they\'re located near sensitive areas in your brain, making surgery risky. In these situations, your doctor removes as much of the tumor as is safe.
        \nEven removing a portion of the brain tumor may help reduce your signs and symptoms.
        \nSurgery to remove a brain tumor carries risks, such as infection and bleeding. Other risks may depend on the part of your brain where your tumor is located. For instance, surgery on a tumor near nerves that connect to your eyes may carry a risk of vision loss.</string>

    <string name="brainTumorTreatmentText3">Radiation therapy uses high-energy beams, such as X-rays or protons, to kill tumor cells. Radiation therapy can come from a machine outside your body (external beam radiation), or, very rarely, radiation can be placed inside your body close to your brain tumor (brachytherapy).
        \nExternal beam radiation can focus just on the area of your brain where the tumor is located, or it can be applied to your entire brain (whole-brain radiation). Whole-brain radiation is most often used to treat cancer that spreads to the brain from some other part of the body and forms multiple tumors in the brain.
        \nTraditionally, radiation therapy uses X-rays, but a newer form of this treatment uses proton beams. Proton beam therapy allows doctors to control the radiation more precisely. It may be helpful for treating brain tumors in children and tumors that are very close to sensitive areas of the brain. Proton beam therapy isn\'t as widely available as traditional X-ray radiation therapy.
        \nSide effects of radiation therapy depend on the type and dose of radiation you receive. Common side effects during or immediately following radiation include fatigue, headaches, memory loss, scalp irritation and hair loss.</string>

    <string name="brainTumorTreatmentText4">Stereotactic radiosurgery is not a form of surgery in the traditional sense. Instead, radiosurgery uses multiple beams of radiation to give a highly focused form of radiation treatment to kill the tumor cells in a very small area. Each beam of radiation isn\'t particularly powerful, but the point where all the beams meet — at the brain tumor — receives a very large dose of radiation to kill the tumor cells.
        \nThere are different types of technology used in radiosurgery to deliver radiation to treat brain tumors, such as a Gamma Knife or linear accelerator.
        \nRadiosurgery is typically done in one treatment, and usually you can go home the same day.</string>

    <string name="brainTumorTreatmentText5">Chemotherapy uses drugs to kill tumor cells. Chemotherapy drugs can be taken orally in pill form or injected into a vein (intravenously). The chemotherapy drug used most often to treat brain tumors is temozolomide (Temodar). Other chemotherapy drugs may be recommended depending on the type of cancer.
        \nChemotherapy side effects depend on the type and dose of drugs you receive. Chemotherapy can cause nausea, vomiting and hair loss.
        \nTests of your brain tumor cells can determine whether chemotherapy will be helpful for you. The type of brain tumor you have also is helpful in determining whether to recommend chemotherapy.</string>

    <string name="brainTumorTreatmentText6">Targeted drug treatments focus on specific abnormalities present within cancer cells. By blocking these abnormalities, targeted drug treatments can cause cancer cells to die.
       \nTargeted therapy drugs are available for certain types of brain tumors, and many more are being studied in clinical trials. Your doctor may have your tumor cells tested to see whether targeted therapy is likely to be an effective treatment for your brain tumor.</string>

    <string name="brainTumorTreatmentText7">
        Because brain tumors can develop in parts of the brain that control motor skills, speech, vision and thinking, rehabilitation may be a necessary part of recovery. Depending on your needs, your doctor may refer you to:\n\n
        <ul>
            <li>Physical therapy to help you regain lost motor skills or muscle strength.</li>\n
            <li>Occupational therapy to help you get back to your normal daily activities, including work, after a brain tumor or other illness.</li>\n
            <li>Speech therapy with specialists in speech difficulties (speech pathologists) to help if you have difficulty speaking.</li>\n
            <li>Tutoring for school-age children to help kids cope with changes in their memory and thinking after a brain tumor.</li>\n
        </ul>
    </string>

    <string name="feedbackCardDescText">A health app is categorized by the FDA as mobile software that diagnoses, tracks, or treats disease. A wellness app is a mobile software that enhances or tracks the overall health of the user. These apps can address mental, physical, social, environmental, or even spiritual factors that relate to overall health.
    </string>

    <string name="feedbackPostCommentText">This apps is very useful to me. I am vey happy to this. But think, if many Prescription saved option is have so that very useful to us. Thanks</string>

    <string name="brain_tumor_characteristics">The characteristics of a brain tumor can vary depending on its type, location, size, and rate of growth. Common characteristics include:
     \n\n<b>1. Location:</b> Brain tumors can occur in different areas of the brain, such as the cerebral hemispheres, cerebellum, brain stem, or pituitary gland.
     \n\n<b>2. Size: Tumors</b> can range in size from small and localized to large and invasive, potentially affecting multiple brain regions.
     \n\n<b>3. Growth rate:</b> Some brain tumors grow slowly over a long period, while others may grow rapidly and aggressively.
     \n\n<b>4. Invasiveness:</b> Malignant brain tumors can invade nearby healthy brain tissue, making complete removal challenging.</string>

    <string name="brain_tumor_types">There are various types of brain tumors, including:
        \n\n<b>1. Gliomas:</b> The most common type, originating from the glial cells that support and nourish the neurons. Gliomas include astrocytomas, oligodendrogliomas, and ependymomas.
        \n\n<b>2. Meningiomas:</b> Arising from the meninges, the protective membranes covering the brain and spinal cord. Meningiomas are often benign.
        \n\n<b>3. Pituitary adenomas:</b> Tumors that develop in the pituitary gland, a small gland at the base of the brain that regulates hormone production.
        \n\n<b>4. Medulloblastomas:</b> Common in children, these tumors occur in the cerebellum and can spread to other parts of the central nervous system.
        \n\n<b>5. Metastatic tumors:</b> Secondary brain tumors that result from cancer spreading from another part of the body, such as the lung, breast, or skin.</string>

    <string name="brain_tumor_symptom">The symptoms and signs of a brain tumor can vary depending on its location and size. Common symptoms may include:
        \n\n<b>1. Headaches:</b> Often persistent and worsen over time, especially in the morning or after physical activity.
        \n\n<b>2. Seizures:</b> Sudden, uncontrolled electrical disturbances in the brain, leading to convulsions or loss of consciousness.
        \n\n<b>3. Cognitive and neurological changes:</b> Memory problems, confusion, difficulty concentrating, personality changes, weakness, numbness, or problems with coordination.
        \n\n<b>4. Visual and hearing disturbances:</b> Blurred vision, double vision, partial or complete loss of vision, and hearing difficulties.
        \n\n<b>5. Nausea and vomiting:</b> Often unrelated to digestive issues and typically more severe in the morning.
        \n\n<b>6. Speech and language difficulties:</b> Slurred speech, difficulty finding words, or understanding language.
        \n\n<b>7. Changes in mood or behavior:</b> Depression, irritability, anxiety, or emotional instability.</string>

<!--    <string name="pituitary_symptom">The symptoms and signs of gliomas depend on the size, location, and rate of growth of the tumor. Common symptoms include:-->
<!--        \n\n1. Headaches-->
<!--        \n\n2. Seizures-->
<!--        \n\n3. Cognitive and memory problems-->
<!--        \n\n4. Changes in personality or behavior-->
<!--        \n\n5. Weakness or numbness in the limbs-->
<!--        \n\n6. Visual disturbances-->
<!--        \n\n7. Difficulty speaking or understanding language-->
<!--        \n\n8. Problems with balance and coordination</string>-->

<!--    <string name="pituitary_diagnosis">Diagnosing a glioma usually involves the following steps:-->
<!--        \n\n<b>1. Medical history and physical examination:</b> The doctor will review your medical history and perform a neurological examination to assess brain function.-->
<!--        \n\n<b>2. Imaging tests:</b> Magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) or computed tomography (CT) scans are used to visualize the brain and detect any abnormalities.-->
<!--        \n\n<b>3. Biopsy:</b> A sample of the tumor tissue is extracted through surgery or a minimally invasive procedure to determine the type and grade of the glioma.-->
<!--        \n\n<b>4. Genetic testing:</b> Molecular profiling of the tumor may be performed to identify specific genetic mutations that can guide treatment decisions.-->
<!--    </string>-->

<!--    <string name="pituitary_treatment">Treatment options for gliomas depend on the type, grade, size, and location of the tumor. Common treatment modalities include:-->
<!--        \n\n<b>1. Surgery:</b> The main goal is to remove as much of the tumor as possible while minimizing damage to healthy brain tissue. In some cases, complete removal may not be feasible due to the tumors location.-->
<!--        \n\n<b>2. Radiation therapy:</b> High-energy beams, such as X-rays or protons, are used to target and destroy remaining tumor cells after surgery or to control tumor growth in inoperable cases.-->
<!--        \n\n<b>3. Chemotherapy:</b> Medications are administered orally or intravenously to kill cancer cells or inhibit their growth. Chemotherapy may be used alone or in combination with other treatments.-->
<!--        \n\n<b>4. Targeted therapy:</b> Certain genetic mutations present in gliomas can be targeted with specific drugs to disrupt tumor growth pathways.-->
<!--        \n\n<b>5. Immunotherapy:</b> This approach aims to stimulate the body's immune system to recognize and attack cancer cells.-->
<!--        \n\n<b>6. Supportive care:</b> Symptom management, rehabilitation, and supportive therapies, such as physical therapy or counseling, can help improve quality of life and alleviate symptoms.-->
<!--        \n\nThe choice of treatment depends on factors like the tumor type, grade, location, and the individual's overall health. Treatment plans are often developed by a multidisciplinary team of healthcare professionals, including neurosurgeons, oncologists, radiation therapists, and other specialists.-->
<!--    </string>-->
    
<!--    <string name="symptoms">The treatment approach for meningiomas depends on various factors such as the tumor size, location, grade, and individual patient considerations. The treatment options may include:-->
<!--        \n\n<b>1. Observation:</b> If the meningioma is small, slow-growing, and not causing significant symptoms, it may be monitored over time with regular imaging.-->
<!--        \n\n<b>2. Surgery:</b> The primary treatment for meningiomas involves surgical removal of the tumor whenever possible. The goal is to achieve complete resection while minimizing damage to surrounding brain tissue.-->
<!--        \n\n<b>3. Radiation Therapy:</b> In cases where complete surgical removal is not feasible or the tumor recurs, radiation therapy may be used to destroy or control the tumor cells.-->
<!--        \n\n<b>4. Medications:</b> Certain medications, such as hormone therapy, may be used for recurrent or progressive meningiomas, particularly those that are hormone-sensitive.-->
<!--        \n\n<b>5. Clinical Trials:</b> Participation in clinical trials may be an option for some patients.</string>-->
</resources>